const quiz = [
    {
        question: "Which type of JavaScript language is ______ ?",
        options: ['Object-Oriented','Object-Based','Assembly-language','High-level'],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression: ?",
        options: ['Alternative to if-else','Switch statement','If-then-else statement','immediate if'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "what is a block of statement?",
        options: ['Conditional block','block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement','both conditional block and a single statement','block that contains a single statement'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do: ?",
        options: ['Shows a warning','Prompts to complete the statement','Throws an error','Ignores the statements'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "The \"function\" and \" var\" are known as: ?",
        options: ['Keywords','Data-types','Declaration statements','Prototypes'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code ?",
        options: ['Preprocessor','Triggering Event','RMI','Function/Method'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning ?",
        options: ['00','0X','0x','both 0x and 0X'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "which one of the following is not considered as an error: ?",
        options: ['Syntax error','Missing of semicolons','Division by zero','Missing of Bracket'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number ?",
        options: ['toString()','valueOf()','toLocaleString()','toPrecision()'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the correct snippet from the following to check if the variable \"a\" is not equal the \"NULL\": ?",
        options: ['if(a!==null)','if (a!)','if(a!null)','if(a!=null)'],
        answer: 0
    }
]